[{"answer": "His dad couldn't be trusted.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 1, "question": "Tonight, is Kim Jong-Il's son just as dangerous as his father?", "qSentId": 0}, {"answer": "This is PIERS MORGAN TONIGHT.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "How many times have you been properly loved?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, we have a shared interest in the outcome.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "If you were President Obama would you be picking the phone up now to the Chinese to make sure there is nothing untoward that now happens?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I think that we all think -- are very cynical about this.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "I mean this is just a stunt, isn't it, for western media eyes?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "North Korea as a state has a considerable blackmailing capability because they have a large concentration of artillery aimed at the city of Seoul, which is the capital of South Korea, and has a very large population.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "How dangerous is North Korea right now?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "I have tried to stay out of the debate but in the Republican Party.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "When you look at all the candidates for the Republican race to be president, which one of them from their foreign policy statements is the one that you think is most suited to be president of the United States?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, the voice alone.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Would you find him sexy through his voice, his brain?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "I mean my pants fell of during the commercial break.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Amazing voice, isn't it?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "You mean like the old Moviefone guy?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, my Twitter is called @kathygriffin, and if you want to send them to a real star, send them to me.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Who is in charge here?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "I really live for that night.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Are you looking forward to humiliating Anderson on New Year's Eve?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "I'm going to drunk dial Wolf Blitzer.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What is a roofie?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "I just haven't heard it called a roofie before.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Are there cards?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "I do fancy him.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Do you fancy him?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, the name of the special is funny, \"Tired Hooker.\"", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Can you save this shameless plug until later?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I get what I want --", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "You're not going to go back to Dr. Kissinger?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I'm living.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "You must be sad that Herman Cain is not in the race any more, aren't you?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Well, it changes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Who's the biggest nut bag?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Let me ask you, though, about him.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Correct?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Why wouldn't I be?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Was that an old time --", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "What's more embarrassing than this moment for me?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Yes, I know, it was great.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "But that is utterly embarrassing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Because unlike you, I'm among the people.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "How did you feel when you woke up?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "And you lost complete control.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Oh, really?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "You may call me whatever you like.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "May I call you Piersy?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "RIFFIN: I've still got a banging bikini bod which is really -- it's a burden at this point.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "What have you still got?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Are you dating a younger man?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Youngerish.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "How much younger?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "A few.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Like how many years?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "More than four years younger.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Is he more than 10?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "More than 20 years?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "You SOB.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "So 15 years?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Are you and this man on the picture right now having sex?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "No, but --", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Is he?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I'm excited you think he's legal.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Fifteen?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Well, I think that there is -- I think I have a better chance of being asked out by a younger guy than a guy my age, for sure.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Do you recommend toy boys?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "I'm 46 but I look younger.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "How old are you?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "My fourth Grammy nomination in a row.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "You ever won?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "No, I'm bitter.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Do you mind just never winning or not?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Aren't they?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "No, you're there to win.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Why else would you be there?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "RIFFIN: No, it's A.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Unlike you who spent your life on the D-list, is that right?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "I like how you're basically making me the new Madonna.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "He's a little old for me.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Somebody here said, would you date Kim Jong-un, the new leader of North Korea?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Do they mean my physical body or my personality.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "How much of Kathy Griffin is fake?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Do you know you're on television?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, the body part is all real, although I did have lypo one time.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "How much have you spent looking this young?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "None of it.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "-- thing you spent money on body-wise that you're most proud of?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "You said if Ryan gets \"The Today Show, you will never be watching it because you hate him.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Do you know her?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Did you go to Kendall's Super Sweet 16?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "I don't think I heard you correctly, because I think you said work ethic.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Don't you admire their work ethic?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "That's heaven for me.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "What did you make of the extensive 72-day marriage?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "I love that you think they started with true love.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Was it a scam or do you think true love just hit a rocky path?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "A certain age?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "I love that you think I have a position.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "-- dating a much younger guy and then marrying him -- I mean, do you worry about your position?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Why don't we talk about --", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "I assume we were talking about that?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Yes, that was so much fun to do that show.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "You must miss it, don't you?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Look, I'm not in the class with those women.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "What is the secret to getting away with looking hot in your 60s, 70s?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "I admire those chicks.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Who do you most admire?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "You just did.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "And you know, Gloria Steinem gave me this great hilarious lecture about how -- can you say vagina on CNN?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "This goes -- then I go to Glo Vanderbilt's house, who says no, no, no, don't worry; your vagina is fine.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "Where are you going with this?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "Probably --", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "What do you got, Piersy?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "What we call in Britain my P-45.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "Are you going to tear me up?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "Everyone wants --", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Who would care?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "That's a spin-off of \"Little People, Big World.\"", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "Who cares?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "No idea.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "What's with my neck?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 771, "question": "Can I be honest?", "qSentId": 770}, {"answer": "I haven't gotten you fired.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "You know what you've done --", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "What is your address, real quick?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "You've shown that you can do live TV with the best of them.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "What's your phone number?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "You're always getting bleeped.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "Did I get bleeped there or not?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "Nothing really.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "OK, what's your question?", "qSentId": 806}, {"answer": "There we are.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 822, "question": "She's driving up or what?", "qSentId": 821}, {"answer": "I love her.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 831, "question": "What do you think of Lindsay Lohan?", "qSentId": 830}, {"answer": "Because the only possibly useful thing about you is you are well connected.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 842, "question": "I don't know -- how can I help you get off the desk?", "qSentId": 841}, {"answer": "I'm sorry.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 849, "question": "Can you get me Cher?", "qSentId": 848}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 854, "question": "Did you come out during the commercial break?", "qSentId": 853}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "Are you an openly gay man?", "qSentId": 855}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 864, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 863}, {"answer": "Surprisingly interesting.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 867, "question": "Who turned out to be surprisingly interesting in the chair?", "qSentId": 866}, {"answer": "Now that you mention it.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 876, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 875}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 919, "question": "You wanted Kissinger for the hour?", "qSentId": 918}, {"answer": "We couldn't.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 930, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 929}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 934, "question": "Could be better than you?", "qSentId": 933}, {"answer": "Because he has given no television interview in 40 years.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 939, "question": "But why on Earth would he ever sit down with you?", "qSentId": 938}, {"answer": "I'm a huge fan.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 943, "question": "What do you bring to the table, Morgan?", "qSentId": 942}, {"answer": "It's very funny.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 965, "question": "Why should anybody watch it?", "qSentId": 964}, {"answer": "You are insane.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 972, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 971}, {"answer": "Have I properly been in love.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 977, "question": "How many times?", "qSentId": 976}, {"answer": "It would -- I would relive the first five minutes of this show.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 994, "question": "If I could give you five minutes to live, and you could relive any moment of your life, what would it be?", "qSentId": 993}, {"answer": "No, I'm just not serious with you.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 1019, "question": "Why are you never serious?", "qSentId": 1018}, {"answer": "I have trust issues.", "docId": "111219pmt", "aSentId": 1021, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 1020}]